<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://haeryny.github.io/haehae/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://haeryny.github.io/haehae/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-02-05T22:26:51-06:00</updated><id>https://haeryny.github.io/haehae/feed.xml</id><title type="html">haeryn yu</title><subtitle>My Blogs for Trimester 2</subtitle><entry><title type="html">5.3-4 Hacks</title><link href="https://haeryny.github.io/haehae/week21/2023/02/05/5.3-4-Hacks.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="5.3-4 Hacks" /><published>2023-02-05T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-02-05T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://haeryny.github.io/haehae/week21/2023/02/05/5.3-4-Hacks</id><author><name></name></author><category term="week21" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[5.3 Summary What is bias in computing? A computer algorithm or software that unfairly favors one input or population over another is said to have computing bias. This can have happened accidentally or on purpose. The HP facial recognition algorithm, which performs better on those with lighter skin tones, is one illustration of computational prejudice. This is probably due to a lack of experience working with persons who have darker skin tones.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Performance Task Blog</title><link href="https://haeryny.github.io/haehae/markdown/week20/2023/01/30/Performance-Task.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Performance Task Blog" /><published>2023-01-30T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-30T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://haeryny.github.io/haehae/markdown/week20/2023/01/30/Performance-Task</id><author><name></name></author><category term="markdown" /><category term="week20" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Performance Task]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Practice MC</title><link href="https://haeryny.github.io/haehae/week20/2023/01/29/Practice-MC.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Practice MC" /><published>2023-01-29T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-29T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://haeryny.github.io/haehae/week20/2023/01/29/Practice-MC</id><author><name></name></author><category term="week20" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Collegeboard MC Score I got 38/50]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Notes from Presentation</title><link href="https://haeryny.github.io/haehae/week19/2023/01/24/Notes-From-Presentation.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Notes from Presentation" /><published>2023-01-24T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-24T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://haeryny.github.io/haehae/week19/2023/01/24/Notes-From-Presentation</id><author><name></name></author><category term="week19" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notes Listing the purposes of the project Listing the features and why they are connected to the purpose/project How the features work, what the limits are and what it is currently doing. What you want to plan for the feature in the future. Showing how some features can do CRUD What the feature is with the picture and accurate design, screenshots of what the person does Tells roles of the person and what they did specifically for the project Reason of why they created this project and how it is connected to the community and real world Talk of the “Model, View, Control Flow” She is showing the API and the users that are created throughout and how the users are used and basically data abstraction used in the program. Showing the importance of the project She created a search option, an ability to log hours, to add clubs, to show clubs in an organized manner Showing the basic overview that shows the API and database and the basic coding for backend in general using flow charts. Shows the plan of project development (scrumboard) through spreadsheats Shows the manifesto]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">5.1-2 Hacks</title><link href="https://haeryny.github.io/haehae/week19/2023/01/24/5.1-2-Hacks.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="5.1-2 Hacks" /><published>2023-01-24T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-24T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://haeryny.github.io/haehae/week19/2023/01/24/5.1-2-Hacks</id><author><name></name></author><category term="week19" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[5.1 Hacks Come up with three of your own Beneficial and corresponding Harmful Effects of Computing Beneficial Helps people with planning trips Gives honest feedback/reviews about different activities and places, which then they could use to improve on those activities and places. Lets people know the best local and tourist parts of a trip that people should go to. Harmful: Can have biased information Can potentially spread hate or negative about specific places/people/activities, which would cause those places to be less popular -Can have spam accounts to promote certain places/activities or karens/bots on the website Talk about dopamine issues above. Real? Parent conspiracy? Anything that is impacting your personal study and success in High School? Dopamine disorders exist. Whether it is pleasant/beneficial or negative/harmful, when someone engages in behavior that releases dopamine, they will seek that happy sensation again and hence engage in that behavior more frequently. Most likely, an addiction would grow, becoming highly time-consuming and distracting from other significant elements of your life, making it a top priority.]]></summary></entry></feed>